Why are you still following me?
Stop pretending, Brother Qingxuan.
This road leads to Tushan.
What?
Afraid we'll hold you back?
Are you sure you want to follow me to die?
Ancestor,
you are mistaken.
We are not going to slaughter demons this time,
but to save someone.
Besides, with the two of us here,
our chances of winning should be higher.
We at Sitiantai are demon hunters.
We don't need to report to you about going to Tushan, do we?
My immortal body is damaged now.
I'm afraid I can't protect you.
If anything goes wrong,
at best, you'll lose a thousand years of cultivation.
At worst, your core and spirit will be destroyed,
never to recover.
As for you,
once you lose your life...
Then you'll have nothing left.
Don't worry.
I will bear
all the consequences.
Me too.
Hyah!
What is this?
What thing?
The Golden Immortal's disciple.
His aptitude is ordinary.
He is nothing special.
Will the Golden Immortal come to Tushan for him?
Your Highness.
The Golden Immortal has people from the Sitian Bureau by his side.
It is truly difficult to deal with.
So we can only start with his disciple.
Please calm down, Your Highness.
How can I calm down?
I cut off the Golden Immortal's immortal root.
He will definitely not let this go.
Rest assured, Your Highness.
We will wait for him for three days.
If he doesn't come,
I will go meet him again.
Thank you for sparing my life, My Lady.
Since you were capable enough to sever his immortal root,
why didn't you bring him back as well?
In the Upper Realm,
I am on par with the Hong Sword.
There is a world of difference between me and a Golden Immortal.
Qingxuan achieved godhood in a single thought after hundreds of thousands of years.
Though he is merely a gatekeeper of Sanshanliu,
his combat power
and cultivation
are above all minor gods.
Severing his immortal root
was just a desperate act of quick thinking.
Whether it was severed completely
is still uncertain.
And even if his immortal body is sealed,
I can't be sure I can defeat him.
In that case,
I will wait for him for three days.
If he doesn't come,
I will go in person.
Li,
you must remember,
you are now Jinwang.
You are no longer an ancient artifact of the Heavenly Realm.
You cannot escape my grasp.
I would not dare.
Take this little thing down and look after it well.
Don't let it get eaten.
I'm so hungry.
I left in such a hurry.
I didn't bring any food.
Who told you not to bring food?
What were you doing earlier?
Then I'll help myself.
If only Feilu were here.
His roasted rabbit is so delicious.
Ancestor,
that Jinwang,
you know him?
He held a post in heaven.
Why did he come down to be a monster?
I'm not trying to pry into your past.
I just think
if we know our enemy and know ourselves,
it's better to have some understanding of him.
After all,
what happened in Ercheng
is too bizarre.
He is not a deity,
and has no divine post.
He is a weapon,
an ancient divine artifact.
A divine artifact.
In ancient times,
the four pillars collapsed,
and the sky couldn't cover the earth.
The high goddess Nuwa mended the sky with five-colored stones.
The remaining stones were scattered across the nine provinces.
Two of them are in the immortal realm,
refined by the spiritual spring of Mount Sumeru,
resulting in two weapons with divine power.
One is my sword,
named Hong.
It stays with me in the Sanshan Sect
and can sever the emotions of those turning immortal.
The other one,
in the Guixu Mirror of the Wangchuan River,
named Li,
can sever the immortal roots of deities falling to the mortal realm.
He is like Hong,
but also different.
He has divine consciousness
and a human form.
Severing immortal roots for a long time
accumulated too much resentment,
thus he became Jinwang.
Actually, it's not surprising
that he fell into the demonic path.
I just didn't expect
to meet him here.
Such a powerful guy
is Tu Luohua's subordinate.
How strong must Tu Luohua be?
Are you scared?
Then go back.
Who says I'm scared?
I'm just...
I'm just worried about Feilu.
Ancestor,
I have a question,
I don't know if I should ask
or not.
You see, most of the deities in this world
are mostly
cultivated from the primordial energy of the beginning of heaven and earth,
the essence of the sun and moon,
or mountains, rivers, and plants.
For example, Nuwa
originated from primal chaos.
Queen Mother of the West is related to the spiritual energy of the Kunlun Mountains.
Some ancient gods were formed by the essence of the Great Dao.
Of course,
there are also those who attained enlightenment through later cultivation.
So what opportunity did you get?
cultivated into an immortal.
Yes, I also want to know
what you transformed from.
I'm not a monster.
What could I have transformed from?
Since I became conscious,
I wandered in the chaos of the three realms.
After attaining enlightenment,
I joined Nuwa's sect
and became a minor immortal guarding the Three Mountains Stream.
Nuwa's sect?
And a minor immortal? I really...
Brother Qingxuan,
what does the immortal realm look like?
If I become an immortal in the future,
where will I go?
It's a long story.
Tu Luohua,
now my immortal root is suppressed,
and I don't know her origin.
If I encounter her,
I don't have full confidence either.
In Er City,
with your divine power and murderous intent,
did you look like your immortal root was destroyed?
What does it matter to you?
Then why does Sitian Tower,
knowing there is such a powerful monster,
not send troops to eliminate it?
Monsters
are also beings of this world.
A great monster is rarely seen in ten thousand years.
Tu Luohua has already become the Monster King.
Even if the court and Sitian Tower dispatch troops,
to be honest,
even if they manage to take down Tu Luohua,
they would have to pay a heavy price.
By then, the court would be shaken,
and the world would be in chaos.
Which is more important
is clear at a glance.
Can you understand?
Never mind.
Since we are in the mortal world,
let's follow its ways.
High God.
It's you.
You still remember me.
I remember everyone
who ascended from Sanshanliu.
Why are you here?
Since my ascension,
I obeyed the mandate of heaven
and was sent to Zhexian Terrace
to manage the banishment of immortals.
I heard you were here,
so I came for a chat.
High God.
If you want to persuade me,
don't even start.
Not at all.
How could I dare to question
what you have decided?
Going this time,
do you have a destination?
This time,
it's not a normal reincarnation.
There is no path of rebirth.
My origin and destination
are both unknown.
I know a good place.
Would you care to listen?
Do you still remember?
Where I come from.
Qingqiu.
Ping Jie Qiang Hai.